So after you've started with the tick-tock, this pattern, some of the most common problems that people have is they might catch a stick too close to the center so it turns over, probably wouldn't be as pretty as that, or they catch the stick to close to the end so it turns over too fast.
What you really want to do is find the ideal point, probably pretty close to the end that knock back and forth and spins the stick just around the center point, around this middle point of the stick right there.
Now one way to clean up your pattern a lot is use both sticks.
So instead of just controlling the crystal stick at the top of its throw, you should also push down on the bottom with your other stick like this.
Now if you notices the stick, the crystal stick is actually doing the same thing whether I do this, or whether I do this.
It really shouldn't change.
All that's happening is that I'm getting a little more control over the stick because I have two of my control stick in contact with it, instead of just one like this.
Now this will definitely help you when you start moving into other patterns, because your going to be able to place this bottom stick just correctly and move into other spins and things like that.
So in review, I want you to practice this, and try to get that timing as close as possible.
Get this tick-tock pattern down, and start doing it with both sticks just like this on either side of the center point.
Then we'll move on from there.